Oh, are you here to see Kamijou?
Y-Yeah.
I'm sorry, but his examination schedule was
moved up, so he's in Physical Therapy right now.
Oh, I see... Thank you.
She sure visits a lot, doesn't she?
I'm glad she does. That patient
is in a difficult mental condition.
I hope she's cheering him up.
He was a violin prodigy
before the accident, right?
Even if he were able to walk again,
he'll never be able to play an
instrument for the rest of his life.
Why did it have to be Kyousuke?
My fingers work perfectly,
but what good are they?
Why couldn't it have been
me instead of Kyousuke?
If I used my wish to heal his body,
what would he think about that?
Would he just thank me? Nothing more?
Maybe I just want him to say something else.
I'm such a horrible person.
Now that I think about it,
I was absolutely clueless back then.
I didn't know what it meant to pray for a miracle, nor the price of one.
I'll never forget the promises we exchanged
I still see it when I close my eyes
I'll move forward as I cast off
this darkness engulfing me
How long will it be before
I see that lost future again?
I'll walk upon this Earth,
and pierce this shadowy veil of unease,
as many times as necessary
The clock that's endlessly ticked away
now tells of the beginning
Let's open the once-closed door,
with these unwavering feelings
My heart started racing once again to paint the future
Even if I get stuck in a maze,
the beautiful blue sky will always be waiting for me
So I won't be afraid
No matter what happens next, I won't give in
Miracles and magic do exist
Episode 4
Is that a mole?
There, got it.
Madoka?
Huh?
If you don't hurry up and eat,
you'll be late to school.
Y-Yeah.
What's wrong, Sis?
D-Does it taste bad?
No, it's good.
It's really good.
Dad's cooking tastes so good because I'm alive...
So I kept telling Yuuka,
but she just didn't get it!
She was almost crying, like, "Huh? What?
Did I say something weird again?"
I was trying so hard not to laugh.
Sayaka, about yesterday...
Sorry, can we talk about it later?
Totally weird, right?
Yeah, that's kind of...
While a woman's prime age for childbirth
Past Subjunctive
is based on medical fact,
using this to determine whether she's of marriageable age is a huge mistake.
Meaning that women over thirty clearly still
have the chance for a loving marriage.
Therefore, you shouldn't be
using the past perfect here,
but rather the present progressive tense—
It's like we're in a different
world or something.
Even though nothing about the school or
Hitomi has changed since yesterday,
now I feel like I'm surrounded by strangers.
That's because no one knows.
We're the only ones who know about the witches and Mami.
Nobody else does.
It's like we're living in an entirely different world from them.
Sayaka...
Our world had changed long ago.
We should've realized that sooner.
What about you, Madoka?
Do you still want to
become a magical girl?
Yeah...
I can't blame you for that.
I know it's not fair...
I know I'm just being selfish right now,
but... I just can't...
Just remembering how she died...
makes it hard to breathe.
I'm so scared.
I hate this.
Mami was really kind.
To show us what it takes to fight, she...
Hey, Kyubey, what's going
to happen to this city?
Who will protect everyone from the witches now that Mami's gone?
This has been Mami's
territory for a while now,
but once the other magical girls find out,
they won't stay back for long.
It won't be long before one of them arrives to hunt witches.
But all they care about is finding Grief Seeds,
right? Just like that transfer student.
It's true that Mami was a rare breed.
Most people would
think about personal gain.
Everybody wants to be
rewarded for their actions.
So that means—
But I think only other magical
girls have the right to criticize that.
I understand how you two feel.
It's unfortunate, but I
can't pressure you into it.
I guess this is it.
I need to go search for girls
who need my contract.
I'm sorry, Kyubey.
No, I'm sorry for getting you involved.
It was short, but thank you,
Madoka. It was fun.
I'm sorry.
Tomoe      Mami
Specialty
Tea Sets
British Tea Life
A Tea Magazine
for the
Modern Adult
Tea Sets
I'm sorry I'm so weak...
I'm sorry...
Homura...
You're blaming yourself too
much for this, Kaname Madoka.
Huh?
No one can criticize
the choices you've made.
And even if they did,
I wouldn't allow it.
It seems you've taken
my warning to heart.
Yeah.
If only I had listened to you sooner...
That still wouldn't have
changed Tomoe Mami's fate.
But I was able to change yours.
I'm glad to have saved at least one life.
Y-You know, Homura...
You seem like a veteran, but in
a different way from Mami.
Perhaps. I won't deny it.
Have you seen a lot of
people die like yesterday?
Yes.
How many?
So many that I've lost count.
I wonder if her room
will stay like that forever.
Tomoe Mami had only distant relatives.
I'm sure it'll be a while before anyone reports her missing.
So no one will even know that she died?
That's just how it is.
If someone dies in there,
there is no corpse left behind.
She'll be deemed forever
missing in this world.
That's what happens to
magical girls in the end.
That's horrible...
She fought alone to protect everyone,
but no one will even realize she's dead...
That's terrible.
That's the nature of the contract that grants us the power we hold.
We don't fight to protect people.
We fight for the sake of our own wishes.
If our deaths go unnoticed by others and we're ultimately forgotten by this world...
Then that's just how it is.
I'll remember.
I'll never forget about Mami.
Never!
I see.
Tomoe Mami's lucky to have
someone who thinks that.
Enough to make me jealous.
You too, Homura!
I'll never forget about you either!
I'll never forget how
you saved us yesterday!
Homura?
You're too kind.
Huh?
Don't forget that kindness can sometimes bring forth an even greater sadness.
What are you listening to?
The Girl with the Flaxen Hair.
Oh, by Debussy, right?
It's a beautiful song.
I-I guess I don't strike people as the type who would listen to classical music.
So sometimes people get really surprised when I can name a piece like that.
It's weird, but they seem to respect me more afterward.
It's only because you
taught me all about it.
If not for you, I probably would never have had
the chance to really appreciate this type of music.
Hey, Sayaka...
Huh?
What is it?
Are you torturing me?
Why are you still making me listen to music?
Are you trying to cause me more pain?
I just thought that you loved music, so...
I don't want to listen to anything anymore!
I just sit here listening
to music I can't even play!
I just... I just...
My fingers won't move.
I can't even feel pain anymore.
What use is a hand like this?
It'll be okay.
It'll all work out.
If you don't give up,
I'm sure someday...
They told me to give up.
They said I had no chance
of ever performing again.
My doctor told me personally that
current medical technology can't heal me.
I'll never be able to use my hand again.
It'd take a miracle or some kind of magic,
and there's no such thing.
There is.
Miracles and magic do exist.
I think we could be friends with Homura if we actually communicated.
I wonder why she ended up
fighting with Mami.
Huh?
Hitomi?
Hitomi!
Don't you have practice today?
It's the same as that woman's...
Hitomi!
Hey, Hitomi!
Oh, Kaname. Good evening.
Wh-What's wrong?
Where are you going?
Where?
I'm going somewhere far better than here.
Hitomi...
Oh, yes. You simply must join me!
Yes, that would be just wonderful!
What should I do?
Isn't this...
If only I could get a hold of Homura...
But I forgot to get her cell phone number!
That's right. I'm worthless.
I couldn't even keep
this small factory running.
There's no place for me in
this world anymore. Not now.
Listen up, Madoka.
If you don't handle these things properly,
something terrible could happen.
Our entire family could end up dying.
Make sure you remember that.
No!
You can't do that!
You mustn't interrupt them.
They're performing a holy ritual.
But that's dangerous!
Everyone here will die!
That's right! We are all going on a
journey to another wonderful world!
Do you understand just
how wonderful that is?
Our living bodies are holding us back.
Kaname, I'm sure
you'll understand soon!
Let go!
Wh-What should I do...
What should I do?!
N-No!
This can't be happening!
No! Please!
Someone help me!
I wonder if this is a punishment of some sort.
I'm sure this happened because I'm weak... Because I'm a liar.
That's why...
I'm being punished.
Sayaka?!
Go back to hell!
Man, sorry about that.
That was a close call, wasn't it?
Sayaka... Those clothes...
Huh?
I guess you could say
I had a change of heart.
I'll be fine!
I did all right for my first
time on the job, didn't I?
But...
You...
Hmph.
You're too late, Ms. Transfer Student.
I didn't expect you to come.
I heard Mami kicked the bucket,
so I came all the way out here.
But what gives? This isn't what you told me.
Sorry, but there's already a new magical girl in this area.
She just made a contract
not too long ago, though.
What the hell? That really pisses me off.
But, y'know, I don't think I want to
give such a great area to some rookie.
What are you planning, Kyouko?
Isn't it obvious?
All I have to do is... beat the crap...
out of her.
One day the light of love burning in your eyes
will transcend time
and destroy one of this world's dreams
as it spirals toward the apocalypse
What is it that you seek
now that you're done hesitating?
Is there a glimpse of hope for tomorrow
beyond this greedy admiration?
I want to be armed with the power
to shatter even the darkness in my hand,
just like the ancient magic in my childhood dreams,
the next time I see your innocent smile.
In my trembling hands I hold
the courage of a plucked flower
My feelings are all I can rely on;
the prayer that awakens
the light
Illustrated by   Kobayashi Jin
I guess I'm flying high!
You can count on Magical Girl
Sayaka to protect Mitakihara City!
I will never regret it
Episode 5
I will never regret it.